screenmirrorapp.com 2018-10-18

# Screen Mirror

## Privacy Policy for Screen Mirror

This privacy policy governs your use of the software application Screen Mirror (www.screenmirrorapp.com) for mobile devices that was created by Smart Dato vGmbH. The Application is able to stream your device's screen to a browser over WiFi.

#### What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?

**User Provided Information**  

The Application obtains the information you provide when you download and register the Application. No Registration is required.

When you send us a feedback email we can access your name and your email address.

We may also use the information you provided us to contact your from time to time to provide you with important information, required notices and marketing promotions.

**Camera Information**  

Screen Mirror accesses the camera of your device in order to scan QR codes. Camera images are only used for this purpose and are not shared or transmitted further.

**Screen Information**  

Screen Mirror accesses your devices screen to transmit it to a target brwoser. This data is only transmitted in your local network and is not shared or transmitted further.

**Automatically Collected Information**  

In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, the local IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, information about the way you use the Application and the specific configuration information (local IP address, quality, settings, transmission time) needed to transmit to the target device, i.e. to the target browser. 

#### Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?

This Application does not collect precise information about the location of your mobile device. 

#### Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?

Yes. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;

  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;

  * with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.

  * if Smart Dato vGmbH is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information.

  * to advertisers and third party advertising networks and analytics companies as described in the section below

#### Automatic Data Collection and Advertising

We may work with analytics companies to help us understand how the Application is being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage. We work with advertisers and third party advertising networks, who need to know how you interact with advertising provided in the Application which helps us keep the cost of the Application low. Advertisers and advertising networks use some of the information collected by the Application, including, but not limited to, the unique identification ID of your mobile device and your mobile telephone number. These third parties may also obtain anonymous information about other applications you've downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit, your non-precise location information (e.g., your zip code), and other non-precise location information in order to help analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Application and elsewhere.

#### Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information

We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. 

#### Security

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

#### Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.

#### Your Consent

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing,” means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information.

#### Contact us

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using Screen Mirror, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at apps@smart-dato.com.

Screen Mirror stores no personal information, neither can your streaming screen be stored. All the screen mirroring transmission is held localy, only the network configuration is transmitted to our server in order to provide it to the target device via the website screenmirrorapp.com. We store on our server the length of the screen mirror sessions, the settings of the session (quality, local ip, port). It is impossible to infer from that information something about your identity.  
We do not store your public ip address nor any other personal information. 

Screen Mirror uses Google AdMob and Google Analytics. We have no influence which data this services collect.
